[ar:ZARD]
[ti:グロリアス マインド]
[al:名探偵コナン OP21]
[by:Oscarchuang]
[00:00.00]
[00:01.30]グロリアス マインド　グロリアス スカイ
[00:06.60]おもいきり泣いたら
[00:10.40]昨日までの事は全部忘れよう
[00:16.70]Seaside moon　Seaside sky
[00:22.10]いつまでも変わらぬ
[00:26.00]ココロをもう一度君に届けたい
[00:32.00]グロリアス マインド
[00:36.00]
[00:40.90]So give me the reason why
[00:46.50]Leave me here alone
[00:49.40]The reason why
[00:52.70]I don't know how I feel
[00:55.50]How I feel
[00:58.20]Give me the rhythm-time
[01:02.00]Leave me here alone
[01:05.20]The reason why
[01:08.40]I don't know how I feel
[01:11.70]So must be the true baby
[01:15.50]Shall we end then it's up to me
[01:19.30]Tomorrow is a different day yeah
[01:22.60]And I know when I'm ready
[01:27.20]グロリアス マインド　グロリアス スカイ
[01:32.70]おもいきり泣いたら
[01:36.40]昨日までの事は全部忘れよう
[01:42.70]Seaside moon　Seaside sky
[01:47.80]いつまでも変わらぬ
[01:51.90]ココロをもう一度君に届けたい
[01:58.10]グロリアス マインド
[02:03.00]
[02:42.00]So give me the reason why
[02:47.30]Leave me here alone
[02:50.80]The reason why
[02:53.70]I don't know how I feel
[02:56.80]How I feel
[02:59.00]Give me the rhythm-time
[03:02.90]Leave me here alone
[03:06.00]The reason why
[03:09.00]I don't know how I feel
[03:12.70]So must be the true baby
[03:16.70]Shall we end then it's up to me
[03:20.10]Tomorrow is a different day yeah
[03:23.80]And I know when I'm ready
[03:28.00]グロリアス マインド　グロリアス スカイ
[03:33.60]おもいきり泣いたら
[03:37.20]昨日までの事は全部忘れよう
[03:43.90]Seaside moon　Seaside sky
[03:49.10]いつまでも変わらぬ
[03:53.00]ココロをもう一度君に届けたい
[03:59.00]グロリアス マインド
[04:04.80]ココロをもう一度君に届けたい
[04:10.80]グロリアス マインド
[04:15.00]
