[ar:ZARD]
[ti:永遠(Till the end of time mix)]
[by:Gordon]
[la:ja]
[01:45.49]If you see a beautiful berry red, that's fine
[01:51.73]I hope it reminds you of the days you spent with me
[01:58.36]Wherever you decided and made up your mind
[02:04.93]We can treat with the wind and sail on waves
[02:09.43]you and I
[02:10.86]
[02:11.36]Like a shiny sands of glass will fade into light
[02:17.67]Together we shall find out a secret land of love
[02:23.80]
[02:24.36]Oh,Darlin',tell me if this thing between us is something we'd call everlasting love 
[02:37.37]If I've been never seeing the meaning of love
[02:42.43]There's nothing all worther than do all lose 
[02:47.43]I'll never be afraid
[02:49.49]
[02:49.74]Just to be with you agian
[02:54.93]
